<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20220210</CreaDate><CreaTime>08491200</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>Locations and attributes of fish passage barriers in Idaho.</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Summary&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Fish Barriers&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;There are a number of formal processes which have assessed and compiled barriers to fish movement over the years. Our initial set of anadromous barriers came from the presence/absence data during the Smolt Density and Carrying Capacity studies circa 1989-90. That data was reported in the series like "Idaho Habitat/Natural Production Monitoring. Part 1. General Monitoring Subproject. Annual Report" The first set of diversions (we are working on the second) came from the ongoing program to screen, consolidate, and replace diversions in the upper Salmon River Drainage. The IDFG screen shop maintains that data and reports it to BPA. Those reports are in a series like "Operation, Repair, and Maintenance of Fish Screens in the Salmon River Drainage. Annual Project Closing Report" The other sources of barrier data came from a process headed up by the USFS for distribution updates for westslope cutthroat trout and yellowstone cutthroat trout. The methods and data were reported in "Status of Westslope Cutthroat Trout (Oncorhynchus clarki lewisi) in the United States: 2002" and a similar report for yellowstone cutthroat trout. The update for culverts will come from the national forest inventories. Their methodologies are described in the inventory reports like "Fish Passage at Road Crossings Assessment Boise National Forest FY 2003."&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Details&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Dataset&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Feature Layer&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;November 24, 2021&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Info Updated&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;November 24, 2021&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Data Updated&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;June 28, 2019&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Published Date&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;455 Records&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;View data table&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>Idaho Fish and Game

https://data-idfggis.opendata.arcgis.com/datasets/IDFGgis::fish-barriers/about</idCredit><idCitation><resTitle>Fish Barriers</resTitle></idCitation><searchKeys><keyword>fish</keyword><keyword>barriers</keyword><keyword>Idaho</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20220210</mdDateSt></metadata>
